flutterscape.com 2010-12-29

# Privacy Policy | Japan Shopping at FlutterScape

Please understand that this is the translation of the original Japanese language version for convenience purpose. In the event of a conflict between the Japanese original and this subsequent English translation, the original Japanese language version shall govern.

## netprice Personal Information Protection Policy

netprice, Ltd. (hereinafter “the Company”) recognizes the importance of handling the personal information of its customers and clients who use its services as a business entity handling such information and believes that it is a social responsibility to use and protect personal information in appropriate manners. The Company is committed to the proper protection of personal information and to continuing to take all steps necessary to ensure appropriate handling and security. The Company regards the protection of personal information as critical to its business and has hereby consequently established netprice Personal Information Protection Policy. 

  1. The Company will comply with laws and regulations, government guidelines and other standards relating to the protection of personal information. 
  2. The Company will establish a management system which comply with “Personal Information Protection Management Systems ? Requirements (JIS Q 15001)” and will comply with the system and strictly manage the collection, use and provision of personal information. 
  3. The Company will take steps to prevent personal information from having unauthorized access, loss, destruction, alteration, leakage and other misuse, and should such events occur, take corrective action. 
  4. The acquired personal information will be handled within the scope of the purpose of use specified in the Company’s Privacy Policy and the Company will establish and conduct a confirmation procedure to prevent use beyond this scope. 
  5. The Company will respond in good faith to inquiries and requests, including requests for disclosure, concerning personal information. 
  6. The Company will continue to strengthen its management structure and refine its systems for the protection of personal information. 

    		Established September 27, 2006
    
    		Teruhide Sato, President and CEO
    		netprice, Ltd.

### Privacy Policy of netprice

netprice Ltd. (“the Company”) has established the following Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy stipulates the Company’s policy for the use and management of personal information when the Company operates a website or conducts business. The Company believes that for users to use its services with peace of mind, it is essential to comply with laws and regulations on the protection of personal information and fully enforce the appropriate collection, use and management of personal information inside the Company. 

#### 1.Definition of personal information

As used in this Privacy Policy, personal information denotes information that can be used to identify an individual, either on its own or in combination with other information held by the Company. Personal information includes member IDs, name, genders, email address, telephone number, mailing address, nickname, pen name, birth date, occupation, job title, credit card information, and purchase history. 

#### 2.Purposes of use of personal information

The Company shall use personal information for the following purposes:

  1. Management of memberships and personal information 
  2. Sales (including the conclusion, etc. of an agreement to provide services; this meaning applies below) of products, rights, digital content and services (hereinafter referred to as the “products, etc.” This shall include financial products, etc.) of the Company and third parties 
  3. Running of campaigns, prize planning and questionnaires 
  4. Simplifying the procedures etc. for member registration when using services where member registration is required by the Company or its subsidiaries 
  5. Notification (including notification via email) of matters necessary for the operation of this website 
  6. Advertisement and sales solicitation (including those via email) of the products, etc. of the Company and third parties 
  7. Publishing of email magazines 
  8. Packing and shipping operations of the products, etc. 
  9. Billing calculation and billing 
  10. Provision of services such as points, coupons and mileage (hereinafter referred to as “points, etc.”) 
  11. Introduction of information posted by members or users 
  12. Replies to inquiries and after-sales support 
  13. Research and analysis of marketing data and development of new services 
  14. Compiling statistics and other data for provision to the Company's subsidiaries and partner companies 
  15. Execution of operations when the Company handles personal information under contract for another business entity, etc. 
  16. Enforcement of rights and the performance of obligations based on contracts and laws, etc. 
  17. Recruitment 
  18. Consideration of business alliance 

#### 3\. Management of personal information

The Company appoints a personal information manager in the division responsible for managing personal information. The person specified below ensures that the management of personal information is appropriate. 

    		Kazuya Kawakami
    		Executive Officer Solutions Department.
    		netprice, Ltd.
    		e-mail：privacy@netprice.co.jp

#### 4.Provision of personal information

The Company takes appropriate steps to protect personal information and shall not disclose nor provide it to a third party in a form that allows an individual to be identified without the consent of that individual, except where allowed by the Personal Information Protection Law, and other laws and regulations. 

#### 5.Shared Use of Personal Information

1.The Company and its subsidiaries may make shared use of the personal information indicated in Article 1 for the purposes of use stipulated in Article 2. The manager of personal information shall be as set out in Article 3. 

2.The Company may use the personal information indicated in Article 1 jointly with partner companies as specified below. The personal information manager shall be as stipulated separately. 

*Partner companies making shared use of personal information and their purposes of use

  1. Media Partners 

When the Company provides its services for magazines and other print media, television, radio and the Internet sites, the Company may use personal information jointly with media partners of these media for the purposes of use stipulated in Article 2. 

  2. Mileage Point Service Providers 

The Company may use personal information jointly with mileage and other incentive point service partners for the purpose of offering reward points and other incentive services in collaboration with them 

#### 6.Security

When personal information is provided through this website, it is encrypted using the industry standard encryption method called SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) to protect it from unauthorized access of a third party. The Company shall provide security by using SSL encrypted communication to protect personal information when the Company deems it necessary to do so. The Company also places strict controls on personal information based on the management standard it has predetermined and takes steps to prevent from having access, loss, destruction, alteration, leakage and infection of personal information by establishing a firewall, developing antivirus measures, and taking other action. 

#### 7.Cookie

This website uses the technology known as Cookies. Cookies are the systems for allowing a communications device used by a customer to temporarily retain certain information as data and identify the customer based on the data whenever the customer revisits the website. The Company provides services on the premise that Cookies are used. If the use of Cookies is not authorized, users may not be able to use certain services of the Company. Users of this website can use their browsers to choose whether or not to allow Cookies and the Company asks customers to check their browser settings as necessary. 

#### 8.The Provision of Information for Partner Companies or Linked Websites and Services

The Company is not responsible for the use of personal information that is independently collected at websites linked to this website, such as websites and services of the Company’s partner companies or of third parties that can be accessed through this website. The Company accepts no liability or responsibility for the independent provisions and activities of these websites or companies. The Company advises users to check the privacy policy of each website. 

#### 9.Disclosure, revision and deletion of personal information

The Company shall respond to requests for the disclosure, revision, addition, deletion, discontinuation of use, elimination, cessation of provision to third parties and notification of purposes of use of personal information in accordance with the Personal Information Protection Law and other laws and regulations. If the request does not meet the requirements stipulated by the Personal Information Protection Law and the JISQ15001, the Company may be unable to respond to the request 

#### 10.Method of making a request for the disclosure of personal information

When making a request for the disclosure, revision, addition, deletion, discontinuation of use, elimination, or cessation of provision to third parties of personal information, please complete the specified request form in accordance with procedures separately set out by the Company and send it by post mail to the Personal Information Customer Consultation Service of the Company together with identity documents. In the event of a request for disclosure, please enclose the predetermined fee and postage. 

    		Contact　Personal Information Customer Consultation Service
    		netprice, Ltd.
    		Gotenyama Trust Tower 6th & 7th Floor, 4-7-35 Kitashinagawa,
    		Shinagawa-ku, Tokyo 140-0001 Japan

#### 11.Method of making request for notification of purposes of use of personal information

To request notification of the purposes for which personal information is used, please contact via email to privacy@netprice.co.jp. 

#### 12.Update of Privacy Policy

The Company may revise this Privacy Policy when laws or regulations are changed or as necessary to improve the protection of personal information. On these occasions, the Company shall post the updated Privacy Policy. 

#### 13.Opinions, complaints and objections as to the Privacy Policy

For inquiries about this Privacy Policy and the handling of personal information, please contact the following consultation service: 

    		Inquiries
    
    		Personal Information Customer Consultation Service
    		netprice, Ltd.
    		Gotenyama Trust Tower 6th & 7th Floor, 4-7-35 Kitashinagawa,
    		Shinagawa-ku, Tokyo 140-0001 Japan
    		e-mail：privacy@netprice.co.jp

#####  Established March 30, 2005 Revised September 27, 2006
